<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"  xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/indiabg"
    tools:context=".Activity134">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:fontFamily="sans-serif-black"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"
                android:text="Tourist Attractions"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:textSize="25dp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:text="Napier Museum"
                android:layout_marginTop="1dp"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"/>

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/image1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:src="@drawable/napier" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/editTextTextMultiLine2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:ems="10"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:text="Named after Lord Napier, this art and history museum was established in 1855. An exemplary example of gothic architecture-style, Napier Museum boasts greatly of its natural air conditioning system. It houses an exceptional collection of ornaments, bronze idols, chariots, and ivory carvings. The museum offers insight into the rich and glorious culture and history of Kerala. The great contribution made by Rajput, Mughal, and Tanjore schools of art along with the skillful work by several Chinese, Japanese, and Tibetan artists can be found in here. The Japanese leather figures depicting the epics of Mahabharata and Ramayana catch the eyes of tourists. Napier Museum is certainly one of the most visited tourist places in Trivandrum. Situated in the Museum compound, the ground floor of this place houses India’s oldest zoological garden. Another important feature is Sree Chithra Art Gallery, established by Maharaja Chithira Thirunalin in 1935. The gallery contains epic works from much famed Raja Ravi Varma and Nicholas Roerich. Amid a well-laid-out garden, the zoological park houses a lake and boat club. The park offers an excellent day outing for children and adults alike. It boasts of 75 different species of animals and birds from India, Ethiopia, and Australia. It is also home to the Lion-tailed Macaque, Nilgiri Tahr, Manipur deer, Indian Rhino, Nilgiri Langur, Asiatic Lion and the Royal Bengal Tiger. There is prominent fauna found here along with habitats of giraffe, hippopotamus, zebra, and Cape buffalo."
                android:gravity="start|top"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                tools:ignore="RtlCompat" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:text="Sree Padmanabhaswamy Temple"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"/>
            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/image2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:src="@drawable/sreepadman" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/editTextTextMultiLine3"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:ems="10"
                android:gravity="start|top"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                android:text="Dedicated to Lord Vishnu, Sree Padmanabhaswamy Temple is one of the famous places to visit. This holy shrine is one of the 108 abodes of Lord Vishnu. A large number of devotees throng the temple on multiple occasions. The place of worship has lent its names to the capital city as ‘Thiru’ ‘Anantha’ ‘Puram’, which means Sacred Abode of Lord Anantha Padmanabha. Dravidian style of architecture is prominent in this holy structure. The chief attraction is the deity of Padmanabhaswamy, enshrined in a reclining posture. However, the main deity remains that of Lord Vishnu and his heavenly consorts namely, Sridevi and Bhudevi. The sacred idol is covered with a special ayurveda mixture that helps in keeping the plaster intact and clean. Devotees donate a large sum of money and precious articles in this temple. The assets are believed to be value around 90,000 crores.  The invaluable donations are kept safe in 6 different cellars. Padmanabhaswamy Temple should definitely be included in the itinerary of the places to visit in Trivandrum. Indeed, the temple remains impeccable in appearance and religious sentiments attached to it."
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                tools:ignore="RtlCompat" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:text="Attukal Bhagavathy Temple"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"/>

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/image3"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:src="@drawable/attukalbhaga"/>

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/editTextTextMultiLine4"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:ems="10"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:text="Attukal Bhagavathy Amman Temple is one of the popular shrines in south Kerala, located in Trivandrum city. It is the point where millions of women yearly gather together for the famous Attukal Pongala Festival held in the month of February and March. The principal god of the Attukal Bhagavathy Temple is Attukal Devi or Attukal Bhagavathy. She is deemed to be a manifestation of Goddess Parvathi and is portrayed to have four arms bearing a spear, a sword, a skull and a shield. Besides the deity of Attukal Bhagavathy, there are also statues of Goddess Kali, Lord Shiva, and Lord Ganesha. The temple is decorated with many sculptures, which is an architectural mixture of both Tamil and Kerala history."
                android:gravity="start|top"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                tools:ignore="RtlCompat" />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>