<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"  xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/indiabg"
    tools:context=".Activity208">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:fontFamily="sans-serif-black"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"
                android:text="Hotels (For Stay)"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:textSize="25dp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:text="The Oberoi Udaivilas, Udaipur"
                android:layout_marginTop="1dp"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"/>

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/image1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:src="@drawable/oberoiudaivilas" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/editTextTextMultiLine2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:ems="10"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:text="Fondly known as the “City of Lakes”, Udaipur, the erstwhile capital of the Kingdom of Mewar, is resplendent with vast hilltop forts, palaces, temples and gardens that serve as reminders of its majestic history. Falling in love with the charm of the “City of Lakes” is easy when you are staying at the best hotel in Udaipur: The Oberoi Udaivilas. Located on the banks of Lake Pichola, our 5 star hotel is spread over 1,21,406 square metres of luxuriant gardens, with an intricate layout of interconnecting domes and corridors that reflect the layout of Udaipur itself; whose seven lakes are linked by canals. Superior accommodations, fine restaurants serving signature cuisine and a quiet emphasis on your wellbeing with daily yoga and personally curated spa therapies. All brought alive by the sincere attention to your every need that is distinctively Oberoi."
                android:gravity="start|top"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                tools:ignore="RtlCompat" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:text="Taj Lake Palace, Udaipur"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"/>
            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/image2"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:src="@drawable/tajlakeudai" />

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/editTextTextMultiLine3"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:ems="10"
                android:gravity="start|top"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                android:text="Jag Niwas, constructed between 1743-1746 by Maharana Jagat Singh II, the 62nd custodian of House of Mewar, was used as a summer retreat by the Mewar Royal family over years until Maharana Bhagwat Singh, Mewar of Udaipur in 1963 converted it into a heritage hotel. A jewel floating in the middle of Lake Pichola, Taj Lake Palace is a building made of marble locally sourced from Rajnagar, brought in by bullock carts travelling 66 kms to Udaipur. Architecture influenced from Mughals, predominantly lead by Mewari techniques this heritage hotel in Udaipur has 65 luxurious rooms and 18 grand suites. Restored to its pristine glory, this spectacular palace became world renowned when the James Bond film ‘Octopussy’ was filmed at it. It was the secluded lair of the film’s eponymous Bond Girl. Its location on an island in the midst of a lake affords every room breathtaking views of the neighbouring City Palace, Aravalli Hills, Machla Magra Hills and Jag Mandir. The incomparable location provides the perfect backdrop for the exquisite cuisines at the elegant restaurants of Taj Lake Palace open only to resident guests. Signature speciality restaurants at this palace serve a choice of cuisines. Neel Kamal for authentic Rajasthani and other dishes from India; and the seasonally open-air Bhairo for contemporary European delicacies. In the evening, indulge in signature martinis, cocktails and a grand collection of premium international spirits at the bar, Amrit Sagar. Continue being pampered as a royal at our Jiva Spa in Udaipur, with carefully created treatments drawn from the ancient wellness heritage of India, and the fabled lifestyle and savoir vivre of Indian royalty. This 5 star palace hotel in Udaipur at Lake Pichola continues the tradition of grand soirees and formal levees which were hosted here by the royal family of Udaipur. Known as the Venice of the East, the city of Udaipur, with its elaborate palaces, serene lakes, exotic temples and resplendent gardens, has a lot to offer. Our concierge would be happy to assist you in making arrangements and planning a special tour of the city of lakes in one of our vintage cars."
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                tools:ignore="RtlCompat" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:text="The Leela Palace Udaipur:Udaipur's Only Modern Palace Hotel By Lake Pichola"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:gravity="center_horizontal"/>

            <ImageView
                android:id="@+id/image3"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:src="@drawable/theleela"/>

            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/editTextTextMultiLine4"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:ems="10"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                android:textSize="15dp"
                android:textColor="@color/black"
                android:text="Luxury awaits at The Leela Palace Udaipur with rooms that feature stunning views of the City Palace or Lake Pichola, situated within landscaped grounds. It has an exclusive spa and outdoor pool. Decorated with warm shades of golds and reds, rooms feature local artwork and fine Indian carpets. They come with a flat-screen TV and iPod dock. Marble bathrooms have a bathtub and premium toiletries. Surrounded by loungers, the large outdoor pool has an attached hot tub. Alternatively, enjoy quiet moments at the peaceful Library Bar or take a day trip organised by the tour desk. Soft breezes and views of a starlit sky accompany fine Indian specialities at the Sheesh Mahal. For an international dining experience, guests can head to the Dining Room at The Leela Palace. Located in “the city of lakes”, Leela Palace Udaipur is within 4 km of the City Centre and City Palace Museum. It is 45-minute drive from Maharana Pratap Airport."
                android:gravity="start|top"
                android:inputType="textMultiLine"
                tools:ignore="RtlCompat" />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>